Guide to the North Carolina State University, Athletics, Media Relations Records
North Carolina State University, Athletics, Media Relations Records
- Football, 1895-2007; 1895 2007; In 1892, the first official football game at NC State was played against a local prep school, Raleigh Male Academy; in 1893, State played their first intercollegiate game against Tennessee. The 1895 team was the first to wear the now traditional red and white colore
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 12 Nov. 1977 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Peach Bowl: general information (1 of 2), 31 Dec. 1977 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Peach Bowl: general information (2 of 2), 31 Dec. 1977 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Iowa State (10th Annual Peach Bowl): programs, 31 Dec. 1977 (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - ABC Sports, 1978 (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - Brochure material, 1978 (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - Brochure, 1978 (Box 174, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1978 (Box 174, Folder 5)
  - Fact sheets, 1978 (Box 174, Folder 6)
  - Football press releases, 1978 (Box 174, Folder 7)
  - General information, 1978 (Legalbox 199, Folder 7)
  - General information, 1978-1979 (Legalbox 200, Folder 1)
  - Media guide, 1978 (Box 174, Folder 8)
  - Operation Football, 1978 (Box 174, Folder 9)
  - Play-by-play scoring (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 174, Folder 10)
  - Play-by-play scoring (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 174, Folder 11)
  - Player-of-the-Week nominations, 1978 (Box 174, Folder 12)
  - Pre-season prospectus, 1978 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Recruiting, 1978 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Recruiting: clippings, 1978 (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Schedule, 1978 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - Statistics, 1978 (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - Technician season preview, 1978 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Ticket information, 1978 (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. East Carolina: game information, 9 Sept. 1978 (Box 146, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. East Carolina: program, 9 Sept. 1978 (Box 146, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Syracuse: game information, 16 Sept. 1978 (Box 146, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. Syracuse: program, 16 Sept. 1978 (Box 146, Folder 11)
  - NC State vs. West Virginia: game information, 23 Sept. 1978 (Box 146, Folder 12)
  - NC State vs. West Virginia: program, 23 Sept. 1978 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: game information, 30 Sept. 1978 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: program, 30 Sept. 1978 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: game information, 7 Oct. 1978 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: program, 7 Oct. 1978 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: game information, 21 Oct. 1978 (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: program, 21 Oct. 1978 (Box 147, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Clemson: game information, 28 Oct. 1978 (Box 147, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Clemson: program, 28 Oct. 1978 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: game information, 4 Nov. 1978 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: program, 4 Nov. 1978 (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Penn State: game information, 11 Nov. 1978 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Duke: game information, 18 Nov. 1978 (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 18 Nov. 1978 (Box 148, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Virginia: game information, 25 Nov. 1978 (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Pittsburgh (Tangerine Bowl): clippings, 23 Dec. 1978 (Legalbox 200, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Pittsburgh (Tangerine Bowl): game information, 23 Dec. 1978 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Pittsburgh (Tangerine Bowl): program, 23 Dec. 1978 (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference All-Conference plyers, 1979 (Legalbox 200, Folder 3)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference brochure, 1979 (Legalbox 200, Folder 4)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Football yearbook, 1979 (Box 221, Folder 9)
  - Brochure, schedule, 1979 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1979 (Legalbox 200, Folder 5)
  - Fact sheets, 1979 (Legalbox 200, Folder 6)
  - Football press releases, 1979 (Legalbox 200, Folder 7)
  - General information, 1979 (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Junior Varsity Football general information, 1979 (Legalbox 200, Folder 8)
  - Media guide, 1979 (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous publications, 1979 (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - Operation Football, 1979 (Legalbox 200, Folder 9)
  - Play-by-play scoring, 1979 (Legalbox 200, Folder 10)
  - Players-of-the-Week, 1979 (Legalbox 200, Folder 11)
  - Pre-season Football clippings, 1979 (Legalbox 201, Folder 1)
  - Pre-Spring Prospectus, 1979 (Legalbox 201, Folder 2)
  - Statistics, 1979 (Legalbox 201, Folder 3)
  - Ticket information, 1979 (Box 221, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. East Carolina: game information, 8 Sept. 1979 (Legalbox 201, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. East Carolina: program, 8 Sept. 1979 (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Virginia: game information, 15 Sept. 1979 (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Virginia: program, 15 Sept. 1979 (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. West Virginia: game information, 22 Sept. 1979 (Legalbox 201, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: game information, 29 Sept. 1979 (Legalbox 201, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: program, 29 Sept. 1979 (Box 149, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Auburn: game information, 6 Oct. 1979 (Box 149, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: game information, 13 Oct. 1979 (Legalbox 202, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: program, 13 Oct. 1979 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: game information (1 of 2), 20 Oct. 1979 (Legalbox 202, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: game information (2 of 2), 20 Oct. 1979 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: program, 20 Oct. 1979 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Clemson: game information, 27 Oct. 1979 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: game information, 3 Nov. 1979 (Legalbox 202, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Penn State: game information, 10 Nov. 1979 (Legalbox 202, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Penn State: program, 10 Nov. 1979 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Duke: game information (1 of 2), 17 Nov. 1979 (Legalbox 202, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Duke: game information (2 of 2), 17 Nov. 1979 (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 17 Nov. 1979 (Box 266, Folder 41)
  - All-ACC selections, 1980 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Brochure materials, 1980 (Legalbox 203, Folder 1)
  - Brochure, schedule, 1980 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Fact sheets, 1980 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - Football press releases, 1980 (Legalbox 203, Folder 2)
  - General information, 1980 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - General information, 1980-1984 (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Junior Varsity Football general information, 1980 (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - Managers and trainers, 1980 (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Media guide, 1980 (Box 151, Folder 8)
  - Play-by-play scoring (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 151, Folder 9)
  - Play-by-play scoring (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 151, Folder 10)
  - Player of the Week awards, 1980 (Box 151, Folder 11)
  - Pre-season prospectus, 1980 (Box 151, Folder 12)
  - Recruiting, 1980 (Box 151, Folder 13)
  - Statistics, 1980 (Legalbox 203, Folder 3)
  - Team pictures, 1980 (Box 151, Folder 14)
  - Red-White game, 19 Apr. 1980 (Box 151, Folder 15)
  - NC State vs. William & Mary: game information, 6 Sept. 1980 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Virginia: game information, 20 Sept. 1980 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: game information, 27 Sept. 1980 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: program, 27 Sept. 1980 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: game information, 4 Oct. 1980 (Legalbox 203, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Appalachian State: game information, 11 Oct. 1980 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Appalachian State: program, 11 Oct. 1980 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: game information, 18 Oct. 1980 (Legalbox 203, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Clemson: game information, 25 Oct. 1980 (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Clemson: program, 25 Oct. 1980 (Box 152, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: game information, 1 Nov. 1980 (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Penn State: game information, 8 Nov. 1980 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Penn State: program, 8 Nov. 1980 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Duke: game information, 15 Nov. 1980 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 15 Nov. 1980 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. East Carolina: game information, 27 Nov. 1980 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. East Carolina: program, 27 Nov. 1980 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - All-Conference players, 1981 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference schedule poster, 1981 (Flatfolder 9)
  - Brochure, schedule, 1981 (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1981 (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - Fact Sheets, 1981 (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - Football press releases, 1981 (Legalbox 203, Folder 6)
  - General information (1 of 2), 1981 (Legalbox 203, Folder 7)
  - General information (2 of 2), 1981 (Legalbox 204, Folder 1)
  - Media guide, 1981 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Player of the Week nominations, 1981 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Roster, 1981 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Statistics, 1981 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Statistics, 1981 (Legalbox 204, Folder 2)
  - Superlatives, 1981 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Red-White game, 25 Apr. 1981 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Richmond: game information, 5 Sept. 1981 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Richmond: program, 5 Sept. 1981 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: game information, 12 Sept. 1981 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. East Carolina: game information, 19 Sept. 1981 (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. East Carolina: program, 19 Sept. 1981 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: game information, 26 Sept. 1981 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: program, 26 Sept. 1981 (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Virginia: game information, 3 Oct. 1981 (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Virginia: program, 3 Oct. 1981 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: game information, 17 Oct. 1981 (Legalbox 204, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: program, 17 Oct. 1981 (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Clemson: game information, 24 Oct. 1981 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: game information, 31 Oct. 1981 (Legalbox 204, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Penn State: game information, 7 Nov. 1981 (Legalbox 204, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Penn State: program, 7 Nov. 1981 (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Duke: game information, 14 Nov. 1981 (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 14 Nov. 1981 (Box 266, Folder 42)
  - NC State vs. Miami: game information, 21 Nov. 1981 (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Miami: program, 21 Nov. 1981 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1982 (Legalbox 204, Folder 6)
  - Coaching search, 1982 (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - Football press releases, 1982 (Legalbox 204, Folder 7)
  - General information, 1982 (Box 156, Folder 7)
  - Media guide, 1982 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - NCAA Investigation, Dec. 1982 (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Play-by-play scoring (1 of 2), 1982 (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - Play-by-play scoring (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Roster, 1982 (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Schedule, 1982 (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - Statistics, 1982 (Legalbox 204, Folder 8)
  - Red-White game, 23 Apr. 1982 (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Furman: game information, 4 Sept. 1982 (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Furman: program, 4 Sept. 1982 (Box 157, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. East Carolina: game information, 11 Sept. 1982 (Box 157, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: game information, 18 Sept. 1982 (Box 157, Folder 11)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: game information, 25 Sept. 1982 (Box 157, Folder 12)
  - NC State vs. Virginia: game information, 2 Oct. 1982 (Box 157, Folder 13)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: game information, 17 Oct. 1982 (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Clemson: game information, 23 Oct. 1982 (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Clemson (Textile Bowl): program, 23 Oct. 1982 (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: game information, 30 Oct. 1982 (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Penn State: game information, 6 Nov. 1982 (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Duke: game information, 13 Nov. 1982 (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Miami: game information, 20 Nov. 1982 (Legalbox 204, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1983 (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - General information, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - Football press releases, prospectus, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - Media guide, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Operation Football, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 5)
  - Play-by-play scoring (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 159, Folder 6)
  - Play-by-play scoring (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 159, Folder 7)
  - Recruiting, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 8)
  - Statistics, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 9)
  - Red-White game, 22 Apr. 1983 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. East Carolina: game information, 10 Sept. 1983 (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. The Citadel: game information, 17 Sept. 1983 (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. The Citadel: program, 17 Sept. 1983 (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Virginia: game information, 24 Sept. 1983 (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: game information, 1 Oct. 1983 (Box 160, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Georgia Tech: game information, 8 Oct. 1983 (Box 160, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: game information, 15 Oct. 1983 (Box 160, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Clemson: game information, 22 Oct. 1983 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: game information (1 of 2), 29 Oct. 1983 (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: game information (2 of 2), 29 Oct. 1983 (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Appalachian State: game information, 5 Nov. 1983 (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Duke: game information, 12 Nov. 1983 (Box 161, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 10 Nov. 1983 (Box 266, Folder 43)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: game information, 19 Nov. 1983 (Box 161, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: program, 19 Nov. 1983 (Box 161, Folder 7)
  - ACC Operation Football, 1984 (Box 161, Folder 8)
  - All-Conference candidates, 1984 (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1984 (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - Fact sheets, 1984 (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - Football press releases, 1984 (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - General information, 1984 (Box 162, Folder 5)
  - Media guide, 1984 (Box 162, Folder 6)
  - Photograph, 1984 (Box 162, Folder 7)
  - Play-by-play scoring (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 162, Folder 8)
  - Play-by-play scoring (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 162, Folder 9)
  - Statistics, 1984 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - Alumni game, 14 Apr. 1984 (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Ohio University: game information, 8 Sept. 1984 (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Furman: game information, 15 Sept. 1984 (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: game information, 22 Sept. 1984 (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. East Carolina: game information, 29 Sept. 1984 (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Georgia Tech: game information, 6 Oct. 1984 (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: game information, 13 Oct. 1984 (Box 163, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: game information, 20 Oct. 1984 (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Clemson: game information, 27 Oct. 1984 (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: game information, 3 Nov. 1984 (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Virginia: game information, 10 Nov. 1984 (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Duke: game information, 17 Nov. 1984 (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - ACC Operation Football, 1985 (Legalbox 205, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1985 (Legalbox 205, Folder 2)
  - General information, 1985 (Box 164, Folder 6)
  - General information, 1985 (Legalbox 205, Folder 3)
  - Media guide, 1985 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Schedule, 1985 (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - Statistics, 1985 (Legalbox 205, Folder 4)
  - Alumni game, 13 Apr. 1985 (Legalbox 205, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. East Carolina: game information (1 of 2), 7 Sept. 1985 (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. East Carolina: game information (2 of 2), 7 Sept. 1985 (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. East Carolina: program, 7 Sept. 1985 (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Georgia: game information, 14 Sept. 1985 (Legalbox 205, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: game information, 21 Sept. 1985 (Legalbox 205, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Furman: game information, 28 Sept. 1985 (Legalbox 205, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Furman: program, 28 Sept. 1985 (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Pittsburgh: game information, 12 Oct. 1985 (Legalbox 206, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: game information, 15 Oct. 1985 (Box 165, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: game information, 19 Oct. 1985 (Box 165, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: program, 19 Oct. 1985 (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Clemson: game information, 26 Oct. 1985 (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: game information (1 of 2), 2 Nov. 1985 (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: game information (2 of 2), 2 Nov. 1985 (Box 166, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Virginia: game information, 9 Nov. 1985 (Box 166, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Duke: game information, 16 Nov. 1985 (Box 166, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 16 Nov. 1985 (Box 266, Folder 44)
  - Clippings, 1986 (Legalbox 206, Folder 2)
  - Media guide, 1986 (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - Schedule, 1986 (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - Ticket information, 1986 (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. East Carolina: program, 6 Sept. 1986 (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Pittsburgh: program, 13 Sept. 1986 (Box 167, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Western Carolina: program, 22 Nov. 1986 (Box 167, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Virginia Tech (19th Annual Peach Bowl): program, media guide, 31 Dec. 1986 (Box 167, Folder 7)
  - Football reunion (1940s teams), 1987 (Box 167, Folder 8)
  - Media guide, 1987 (Box 167, Folder 9)
  - Schedule, 1987 (Box 167, Folder 10)
  - Ticket envelopes, 1987 (Box 167, Folder 11)
  - NC State vs. East Carolina: program, 5 Sept. 1987 (Box 167, Folder 12)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: program, 26 Sept. 1987 (Box 167, Folder 13)
  - NC State vs. Georgia Tech: program, 3 Oct. 1987 (Box 167, Folder 14)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: program, 17 Oct. 1987 (Box 167, Folder 15)
  - NC State vs. East Tennessee State: program, 7 Nov. 1987 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 14 Nov. 1987 (Box 273, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Virginia: program, 21 Nov. 1987 (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - Media guide, 1988 (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - Schedule, general information, 1988 (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Western Carolina: program, 3 Sept. 1988 (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: program, 17 Sept. 1988 (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. East Tennessee State: program, 8 Oct. 1988 (Box 168, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. East Tennessee State: program, Oct. 8, 1988 (Box 277, Folder 15)
  - NC State vs. Clemson (Textile Bowl): program, 22 Oct. 1988 (Box 168, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: program, 29 Oct. 1988 (Box 168, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 12 Nov. 1988 (Box 168, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. Pittsburgh: program, 19 Nov. 1988 (Box 168, Folder 11)
  - NC State vs. Iowa (21st Annual Peach Bowl): program, media guide, tickets, bumper sticker, 31 Dec. 1988 (Box 168, Folder 12)
  - Football Banquet program, 25 Jan. 1989 (Box 168, Folder 13)
  - Media guide, 1989 (Box 168, Folder 14)
  - Offensive Lineman School, 18-22 Jun. 1989 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - Schedule, brochure, 1989 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - Ticket information, 1989 (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: program, 2 Sept. 1989 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Georgia Tech: program, 9 Sept. 1989 (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Middle Tennessee: program, 7 Oct. 1989 (Box 169, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 11 Nov. 1989 (Box 273, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Virginia Tech: program, 18 Nov. 1989 (Box 169, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Arizona (Inaugural Copper Bowl): program, media guide, 31 Dec. 1989 (Box 169, Folder 8)
  - Brochures, 1990 (Box 169, Folder 9)
  - Fan survey, 1990 (Box 169, Folder 10)
  - Media guide, 1990 (Box 169, Folder 11)
  - Schedule, 1990 (Box 169, Folder 12)
  - Schedule poster, 1990 (Flatfolder 12)
  - "Stick With the Wolfpack" poster, circa 1990s (Flatfolder 8)
  - Ticket information, 1990 (Box 169, Folder 13)
  - NC State vs. Western Carolina: program, 1 Sept. 1990 (Box 169, Folder 14)
  - NC State vs. Georgia Tech: program, 8 Sept. 1990 (Box 169, Folder 15)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: program, 15 Sept. 1990 (Box 169, Folder 16)
  - NC State vs. Appalachian: program, 6 Oct. 1990 (Box 169, Folder 17)
  - NC State vs. Clemson (10th Annual Textile Bowl): program, 20 Oct. 1990 (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: program, 27 Oct. 1990 (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 10 Nov. 1990 (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - All American Bowl guide, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - 100th Year of Football at NC State, 1991 (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Media guide, 1991 (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Schedule, brochure, 1991 (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - Schedule poster, 1991 (Flatfile 13)
  - Ticket information, 1991 (Box 170, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Virginia Tech: program, 7 Sept. 1991 (Box 170, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Kent State: program, 14 Sept. 1991 (Box 170, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: program, 28 Sept. 1991 (Box 170, Folder 11)
  - NC State vs. Georgia Tech: program, 5 Oct. 1991 (Box 170, Folder 12)
  - NC State vs. Marshall: program, 19 Oct. 1991 (Box 170, Folder 13)
  - NC State vs. Virginia: program, 9 Nov. 1991 (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: program, 23 Nov. 1991 (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - Media guide, 1992 (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - Schedule, brochure, 1992 (Box 171, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 14 Nov. 1992 (Box 171, Folder 5)
  - Schedule, brochure, tickets, 1993 (Box 171, Folder 6)
  - Media guide, 1994 (Box 171, Folder 7)
  - Schedule, brochure, 1994 (Box 171, Folder 8)
  - Schedule poster, 1994 (Flatfolder 10)
  - Ticket information, 1994 (Box 171, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Bowling Green: program, 1 Sept. 1994 (Box 171, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. Western Carolina: program, 24 Sept. 1994 (Box 171, Folder 11)
  - NC State vs. Georgia Tech: program, 1 Oct. 1994 (Box 171, Folder 12)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: program, 15 Oct. 1994 (Box 171, Folder 13)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 12 Nov. 1994 (Box 171, Folder 14)
  - NC State vs. Florida State: program, 19 Nov. 1994 (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - Media guide, 1995 (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - Preseason prospectus, 1995 (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - Schedule, brochure, 1995 (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - Ticket information, 1995 (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Media guide, 1996 (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - Schedule, ticket information, 1996 (Box 172, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Georgia Tech: program ( Wolfpack Game Time Magazine vol. 1, no. 1), 7 Sept. 1996 (Legalbox 214, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Florida State: program ( Wolfpack Game Time Magazine vol. 1, no. 2), 19 Sept. 1996 (Legalbox 214, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Alabama: program ( Wolfpack Game Time Magazine vol. 1, no. 3), 12 Oct. 1996 (Legalbox 214, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program ( Wolfpack Game Time Magazine vol. 1, no. 4) (Legalbox 214, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: program ( Wolfpack Game Time Magazine vol. 1, no. 5), 23 Nov. 1996 (Legalbox 214, Folder 10)
  - Brochure, 1997 (Box 172, Folder 8)
  - Media guide, 1997 (Box 172, Folder 9)
  - Media guide, 1999 (Box 172, Folder 10)
  - Schedule Poster, 1999; 1999 1999 (Oversizeflatbox 274, Folder 2)
  - Media guide, 2000 (Box 172, Folder 11)
  - Media guide, 2001 (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Indiana: program, 6 Sept. 2001 (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Ohio: program, 13 Sept. 2001 (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Virginia: program, 27 Oct. 2001 (Box 173, Folder 4)